Jonathan Grangien

CV/resume

EXPERIENCE

SEPT 2015 - PRESENT

Media Technology Days

Webmaster

Taking in the planning and work behind the exhibition event Media Technology Days (medieteknikdagarna), which aims to inspire and connect students and companies. As webmaster I am responsible for managing the website medieteknikdagarna and things web related.

SEPT 2015 - PRESENT

LiTHehack

Programming Tutor

Taking part in the student-driven organization LiTHehack at Linköping University, I help peers with programming related labs, projects or questions.

SEPT 2015 - OCT 2015

Linköping University

Laboratory Assistant

Worked as a tutor for a couple of laboratory exercises, and provided general help during a two month period project, in the course User Interfaces and Communication at Linköping University.

SOME PUBLIC PROJECTS

2015 Galaxy

(jonathangrangien.se/myGalaxy)

An interactive WebGL application I worked on in a team of five during a comp. graphics course. A user can create planets and customize it among those created by others.

2015 Reverbify

(reverbify.meteor.com)

Hybrid App built as a team project in a sound physics course. The user can upload or record an audio sound clip, and then apply an echo effect from a nice list, and play it back.

2015 Trappans Personalportal

Helped building a staff portal for a local pub/club. I worked on the server side PHP and implemented modern features with dynamic JavaScript.

2014 **Mapus**

An Android app built in a user interface oriented course, designed for students to log in to accounts and set out markers on local maps designated where to study together.

△ Sankt Persgatan 67 A 60233 – Norrköping, Sweden

a +46 73 365 1112

□ jonathan.grangien@gmail.com

www.jonathangrangien.se

SUMMARY

Student of the M.Sc Computer Science in Media Technology engineering programme at Linköping University, Sweden. The courses I have taken at the university – many of which have been group project oriented – have given me good grounds in IT, and I have been able to gain experience through several side engagements. My personal website provides a portfolio.

EDUCATION

2013 - 2018 **MSc comp. sc.**

Mediatechnology

Linköpings Universitet,

Norrköping

2009 - 2012 Natural Science Program

HIGH SCHOOL

NT Gymnasiet, Stockholm

COMMUNICATION SKILLS

SWEDISH Native

ENGLISH Oral: Proficient, written: Proficient

JAPANESE Oral: Good

FRENCH Oral: Basic, written: Good

SOFTWARE SKILL LEVELS

GOOD C++, JavaScript, HTML, CSS,

git, Unix, Vim

INTERMEDIATE Java, Matlab, PHP, LATEX,

MySQL

BASIC Python, Windows, Postgres,

MongoDB